Haruka Inoue
Morning Musume。 25th Anniversary Audition
She passed!
Congratulations!
You have been chosen to join Morning Musume。ヌs 17th term!
Akari Sakurada
Morning Musume。25周年記念オーディション
She passed!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
I have been selected to join Morning Musume。 as a member of the 17th term.
I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto.
I am anxious, but I will do my best with a positive attitude, so thank you very much for your support.
I'm so surprised that my head is fluffy, but I'm very happy.
When I stood here and stood up, I realized.
At first I wondered why you were here.
I am shy and reticent, but I would like to change that and give an imposing performance.
I am Ako Imijeta, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
I would like to give a performance that will convince people that I was chosen for the competition. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
I was full of surprise when I sang, so when I came in for a moment, I was really...
I was so surprised that I was speechless.
Even before I was told that I had been accepted, I was wondering if you would come or not,
I was so happy.
I thought my position was a bit odd, but then I saw Mr. Fukumura, so I was a bit surprised.
I think there are many things only I can do, so I want to practice more and gain confidence,
I would like to perform with my workers.
Now let's meet the new members!
I told everyone in advance that I would meet the new members on this day, not as a surprise.
How do you feel now?
You said I had a dream during the dairy.
You said you had a dream!
I had it again!
Oh, my God!
Again?
Really?
Yes!
There were three of them!
I didn't get a hit at all.
Four!
Maybe we'll win this year.
Let's win it this year!
Yes, sir.
See you. And the 15th term.
And we're accepting new members for the second time.
I don't know. Dailey made a really solid comment earlier.
I'm so excited!
I'm so nervous!
Now that I remember the faces that came in a year ago...
I'm sure!
I'm so nervous!
But I'm ready to accept it now.
I'm ready!
I've seen that face before!
I've seen it before!
With a warm heart
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it
Yes, I'm looking forward to it!
I'm nervous.
I know more now.
We really haven't heard anything about it.
All we know is that it will be announced today.
We don't know how many people are coming or what kind of kids are coming.
I'm nervous about how many people we're going to welcome.
Dozens of people might come in.
Maybe ten.
I've got room in the back for a couple of rows.
We're very receptive today.
May I?
Yes, ma'am.
Now I'd like to invite a new member to join us.
New members, please!
Please introduce yourself.
I am Haruka Inoue, a 17-year-old high school sophomore from Kyoto.
I look forward to working with you.
I am Taishi Inoue, a 14-year-old junior high school student from Shizuoka, Japan.
Please give me your best regards.
So, two from the general public.
Yeah. 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
Congratulations~!
Congratulations!
Let's keep the questions coming from the members.
From members?
Keep asking questions.
Do you have any big animals?
A snake.
Yeah. 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
I'm not good with them right away.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We'll talk about it in the future.
That's funny.
I like rabbits.
I hope you like pandas,I hope you will like Mr. Panda,
Mr. Panda Fitzvah!
Fitzvah!
Do you have a favorite part of meat?
I like tongue.
Oh 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
I like the halami.
Yeah. 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
What should I ask?
What kind of water do you like?
Do you prefer perfume or summer water?
I like summer water.
It's delicious.
I like perfume.
It's a great perfume.
Thank you very much. Such a simple question.
I really like donburi,
Do you have a favorite rice bowl?
I like Kaisendon the best.
I love taco rice.
I also like taco rice.
We eat rice together.
Do you like baseball?
Ask me what my favorite sport is.
I like tennis.
I played in junior high school.
I like soccer.
I have no idea, but I like soccer.
We really only talk about our respective hobbies.
How did you get to know Morning Musume。 How did you get to know Morning Musume。
You are asking me like an audition.
Did you see Morning Musume。 I guess I was watching Morning Musume。
Seeing them perform outdoors,
The latest festivals?
It's a festival.
The old audition shows,
I was allowed to see the 15th period's,
That's how I came to like them.
What is your birthday?
I was born on May 6.
You were born on May 6!
Congratulations!
How old are you now?
I turned 17.
I was born on July 8,
Wow!
I turned 14.
Almost 15.
Blood type?
I am type A.
I'm type A, too.
Type A. Raise your hand.
Thank you.
There are a lot of them.
Did you two know each other at the audition?
Yes, we did.
Did you talk about how you knew each other?
I thought they were rivals.
That's what I thought.
They were looking forward to each other.
You were only conscious of how great they were?
Why don't you introduce them to other people?
From each other's point of view.
I have an audition.
I'd like to get to know them.
He's very firm,
She's very solid, and she's always willing to tell me when I'm wrong.
He is a very good singer,
He is a very good singer, and sometimes he jokes around with me.
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, I just had a meeting with the members, so let's go! Can you go? I said, "Can you go?
No! He said, "No!
Can't you go? Like that.
Can we go? Like that.
He was like that,
But she's kind of shy.
That's right. Haruka is.
That's why I'm going to talk to her a lot,
I hope to get to know her personality better.
Now that I've learned a lot about the two of you,
I would like to go to the photo shoot now.
We will do our best with this 14-member team,
I would like to ask for everyone's support.
Thank you very much.
This is the first time for me to welcome a junior member.
I have only been a member for about a year, maybe a year or so,
But I have a junior colleague joining me at that point,
Both of them are very cute and very strong,
They are both so cute and solid, and I am really looking forward to working with them as Morning Musume。 I am very happy that we are going to compete together as Morning Musume。
I love talking with them.
I hope I can learn a lot about you two,
I hope I can learn a lot about them, and I also hope I can teach them many things from my position as a senior,
I would also like to get to know them well since they joined the company very close to each other.
Also, after the shoot, one of my seniors told me that Riley looked like an older sister,
I was a little happy.
I would like to do my best to be a little older sister.
Oh, speaks Spanish!
This is Masato, isn't it?
I thought it was an audition.
I was very surprised, anxious, and happy when I was told that I passed.I was very surprised, anxious, and happy when I was told that I had passed.
I didn't really feel it at the time.
But when I met the members and took a picture with them
I felt that I was finally going to join the group.
I didn't expect to meet you today.
I was so happy to meet them.
You were so cute, I couldn't look directly at you.
After talking to them for a while.
I thought they were very cheerful people.
I really admired their cool performance.
I would like to do my best to make a cool performance with them.
I'm clumsy, but I'll do my best in my own way, so please support me.
The seniors welcomed me so warmly.
It made me laugh a little and had a lot of fun.
The way they posed for the photo shoot.
I admire them so much.
It's not just singing and dancing.
There are more things I respect.
I'm going to do my best to surpass my seniors.
When Mr. Okumura took our picture
He put his hand on my shoulder when he took my picture.
I really felt like he was a professional.
Since I started auditioning
I've been able to do more and more since I started auditioning.
But after meeting with the senior members today
I realized what I can't do and what I lack.
In my future activities
I want to do my best to improve my good points
I want to do my best.
I will do my best in everything I can do.
Thank you for your support.